Really? Do you have to do this right now?
不是吧? 你非得現在打掃?
Wow,that's the first time anyone ever complained
哇哦 還是頭一次有人抱怨 我活兒干多了啊
Why don't you go do that on the deck?
你怎麼不去陽台上練?
Because... this is my house.
因為... 這是我家
I can work out wherever I want.
我想在哪練就在哪練
Besides,when I do yoga on the deck,the kids on the beach call me gay.
再說 我要是在陽台上練瑜伽 沙灘上的小屁孩們叫我基佬的
You sure that's not because you live with a middle-aged man?
你確定不是因為 你跟個中年男人住一起嗎?
Morning.
早啊
Ooh,a little yoga?
做瑜伽啊?
Yeah,I'm just trying to clear my head.
恩 我想醒醒腦子
Um,speaking of heads,Buddha's poking his out of the temple.
說到頭 佛祖的頭也從廟裡探出來了
You know what? If I lived here alone,it wouldn't matter.
知道嗎? 要是我一個人住 就沒關係了
Right. Sorry. Namaste.
是哦 不好意思 鞠個合十禮
- What does "Namast" actually mean? - Get out!
- "雙手合十"其實到底嘛意思? - 滾!
Okay. I'm gonna "nama-not-stay" right here.
好吧 我這就"快走不留"了
Okay,focus. I want peace... I want serenity...
好了 專心 我但求平靜... 我要寧靜...
I want a murder weapon.
我要個凶器
Dude! You need to relax. Do some yoga or something.
夥計! 別激動 去做點瑜伽什麼的
What is that?
那是什麼?
It's a holistic hangover cure.
用來全面治癒宿醉的
Kale,wheatgrass,three shots of tequila. Cheers.
甘藍 麥草 三杯龍舌蘭 乾杯
You know what? Screw it. I'm gonna stay drunk.
知道嗎? 去他的 我還是繼續醉下去好了
Oh,yikes. Think I ate a little too much ginger last night.
呀 我可能昨晚紅髮女郎 吃得太多了
Oh,you had sushi for dinner?
你昨晚吃壽司了?
Yeah,let's go with that.
好吧 就當是吧
It's crazy,isn't it?
真是瘋了
We finally get rid of Jake,and now we got another one on our hands.
我們好不容易擺脫了Jake 現在又來一個
Yeah,about that... What is the long-range plan here?
是啊 關於這事... 你的長遠計劃是什麼?
I don't know.
我不知道
I always thought we'd spend our golden years together.
我一直覺得 我倆會一起過退休後的歲月
Eventually,maybe sell the beach house,move to the desert,
最終嘛 可能會賣了海景別墅 搬到沙漠裡去
spend our days toiling in our cactus garden.
在我們的仙人掌花園裡辛勤勞作
Yeah,that sounds swell,but...
聽起來不錯 但...
Go out to early bird dinners wearing matching jumpsuits...
穿配套的連體褲一起外出就餐...
Okay. Look,I'm not gonna wear a jump...
好了 聽著 我才不要穿連體...
All right. You know what?
好吧 這樣
Let's try this another way.
我換種方式問
Uh,in your romantic fantasy of our future,where is Jenny?
在你對我們未來的浪漫幻想中 Jenny是個什麼角色?
She'll spend Christmas with us,
她會過來和我們過聖誕節
but we're gonna want our alone time.
但我們會想多些二人世界
Okay,let's focus on that word "alone.
好 說到二人世界
Having house guests is the best.
有客人留宿當然很好
You know,you get excited to see them,
就是 你見到他們會很興奮
you put out the fluffy towels,you hold your farts,everything's nice...
把上好毛巾給他們用 憋住不放屁 一切都很美好...
but,eventually,you have to fart.
但你最終還是要放屁的
Here's what you do.
你可以這麼著
Uh,you go out on the deck,and pretend to look at the ocean,
走到陽台上 假裝看大海
wait for a big wave and when it breaks,so do you.
等過來一個大波浪 浪下去時 你也順著下吧
Alan,I'm putting in a home gym.
Alan 我要建家庭健身房
And it's either going in Jenny's room or Alan's room.
反正不是用Jenny的房間 就是用Alan的房間
It's your call.
你自己決定
Bitch be gone.
這小賤人得走啊
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=伊甸園美劇論壇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET- 雅贝
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組-歆組=- 翻譯: 霄霄 午桑 小Jake 校對: Baby 小貂 時間軸: 雅貝
Two And a Half Men  Season 11 Episode 2 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
好漢兩個半 第十一季 第二集
Here we go.
走起
An appletini a day keeps the doctor away.
日飲蘋果馬提尼 大夫通通都遠離
Cute. And what keeps Alan away?
真伶俐 那什麼能讓Alan遠離?
You.
你
Touch . Why am I here?
說得好 找我來幹嘛?
Oh,I just thought we could get together.
我就想一起坐坐
Maybe find out what's going on in each other's lives.
交流下彼此的生活狀況
There's never anything going on in your life,Alan.
你從來沒什麼生活可言 Alan
Okay,you start.
那行 你先說
All right,let's see...
好吧 我想想...
Well,my boyfriend Marty has just moved in.
我男朋友Marty剛搬進來
Moved in? That's a little fast.
搬進來? 有點太快了吧
He's 91 and a half.
他都91歲半了
He doesn't do anything fast.
他做什麼事都快不起來
So you two sleep in the same room?
那你倆睡一個房間?
If you're trying to find out if we have sex,yes,we do.
如果你是想問我們有沒有做愛 答案是有
Frequently and nastily.
頻繁而且下流
Good God! The man is in a wheelchair.
上帝啊! 那傢伙都坐輪椅了
How do you think he got there?
你覺得他是怎麼坐上的?
No,I was asking if your guest room is available.
不 我是問你的客房空著嗎?
Darling,I-I would love for you to come stay with me,
親愛的 我很想你來跟我們住
but with Marty there now,it's-it's impossible.
但Marty已經搬進來了 那就不可能了
Oh,not me. Jenny.
哦 不是我 是Jenny
Oh,Jennifer can move in.
哦 Jennifer能搬進來
Wait. Why can she move in and not me?
等等 為什麼她能搬進去而我不行?
Darling,if you were a child,this would be one of those situations
親愛的 如果你還是個孩子 在這種情況下
where I would give you five dollars to shut up.
我會給你5塊錢叫你閉嘴
Well,I'm not a kid anymore,Mom.
可我已經不是孩子了 媽媽
How's $20 sound?
20塊怎麼樣?
No,I want to have this conversation.
不 我想和你談談這事
- Forty. - We're done.
- 40塊 - 談話結束
All right,I'm out of here.
好了 我要走了
Don't be a stranger,Jenny.
咱別就此變陌生了 Jenny
I me,I know that you are one but that didn't stop me from letting you stay here.
當然對我來說你是陌生人 可我還是讓你留下了
And that didn't stop me from throwing up in your...
我也還是吐得你滿...
Ah,you know,you'll figure it out.
算了 你遲早會發現的
Um,h-have you got everything?
東西都帶齊了嗎?
Yeah,I think so.
恩 應該帶齊了
There's a girl in my room,uh,Tara,Tanya...
我房裡有個女孩 Tara Tanya之類...
I don't really know what the hell her name is.
不知道她具體叫什麼
It's tattooed right above her ass.
名字紋在她屁股上
Anyway,when she wakes up,will you give her this for cab fare?
隨便啦 反正等她醒了 能把這錢給她打的嗎?
And uh,uh... tell her I,"Mackenzie," will call her if I get back from the Congo.
告訴她 "Mackenzie" 也就是我 如果從剛果回來 會打給她的
See you.
再見了
- Bye. - Take care.
- 拜 - 多保重
Can you believe that?
你能相信嗎?
I know. A Harper left this house voluntarily.
我知道 居然會有姓Harper的 自願離開這房子
And gave me money.
還給了我錢
Hi,Alan.
嗨 Alan
Lyndsey. This is a surprise.
Lyndsey 真是稀客
I know; I-I'm sorry.
我知道 我很抱歉
I just need to talk to you in person.
我想找你當面談談
Oh,yeah,yeah. Come on in.
行啊 行啊 進來吧
Are we alone?
家裡沒人嗎?
Never!
從來不可能!
Hi,Walden.
嗨 Walden
Can we talk in private?
我們能私下談談嗎?
Oh,sure,let's go in my room.
當然 去我房間吧
Oh,uh,hold on a second.
哦 等一下
Okay,we're all set.
好了 一切就緒
Aw,dude,come on!
惡 老兄 拜託!
So what's up?
找我什麼事呢?
Nipple!
我奶頭!
I am so mad at you.
我好生你的氣
Why?
為什麼?
Because I-I'm with Larry now.
因為我已經跟Larry在一起了
He's smart,handsome,successful...
他聰明 英俊 還很成功...
God,you have a type.
老天 你標準不低啊
No. When I'm with him,I can't stop fantasizing about you.
不是 跟他在一起時 我老忍不住想著你
Okay,I-I-I'm confused.
好吧 我糊塗了
I'm getting a chubby,but I'm confused.
我有點勃起 但是好困惑
So you want to get back together?
你是想復合?
Oh,God,no.
上帝 當然不是
I just want to have sex with you.
我就想跟你滾床單
Why? And why am I asking?
為什麼? 這時候我幹嘛問這個?
I don't know. I just know that I do.
我不知道 我就知道我要你
Of course. Forbidden fruit is so much sweeter.
當然了 禁果肯定是更甜美的
Go on,pluck my forbidden fruit.
來吧 來采我的禁果
Pop my cherry. Peel my banana.
摘我的小櫻桃 剝我的香蕉皮
Squeeze my fuzzy peaches.
捏我毛茸茸的桃子
In my fantasy...
在我的幻想中
you don't talk.
你是不說話的
Bye,Walden.
再見 Walden
Bye,Lyndsey.
再見 Lyndsey
Um,is it hot in here or did I just have sex?
是屋裡特別熱 還是我剛嘿咻完?
Did you guys get back together?
你們復合了?
Better.
比那更好
She wants nothing from me except the old Harper harpoon.
除了我的金箍棒 她啥也不要
Know what I'm sayin'?
懂我的意思不?
How is it possible that you're having sex and I'm not?
你有性生活而我沒有 這怎麼可能呢?
Well,apparently,her perfect boyfriend Larry has an Achilles heel...
顯然 她的完美男友也有弱點
and it's on his penis.
弱點就在他的雞雞上
have you guys seen Mackenzie?
你們看到Mackenzie了嗎?
- She went to Cabo. - Congo.
- 她去卡布了 - 是剛果
- She's not here. - She's dead.
- 她不在這裡 - 她死了
In the Congo.
死在剛果
- Sorry,Tanya. - Tara.
- 很抱歉 Tanya - Tara
Alyssa.
是Alyssa
So... Evy tells me you want to be an actress.
Evy告訴我你想當演員
I figured with my daddy issues,it was either that or stripping.
鑒於缺乏父愛 我只能要麼演戲要麼跳脫衣舞了
You've certainly got the rack for either one.
憑你的資質 那兩行都能幹
Bless your heart.
你心腸真好 菩薩保佑你
My heart is in a landfill.
我的原裝心腸埋在垃圾場裡
This baby belonged to a drunken quarterback from Alabama.
現在這顆是移植一個 阿拉巴馬酒鬼四分衛的
Roll Tide!
紅潮!
You know,Marty is a television legend.
Marty是電視界的傳奇人物
He created  Here Comes Pleshkin.
他創作了"普希金來了"
I love that show.
我愛死那個節目了
Th-That was a drinking game in college.
在大學裡有個喝酒比賽
Every time someone would yell "Pleshkin!
每當有人喊普希金
" I would take a shot.
我就乾掉一杯
I had so much drunken sex because of your show.
因為你的節目 我有過無數次酒後亂性
It was a piece of crap,but it paid for my first six...
那節目就是渣渣 可我賺足了養頭六個妻子的錢
seven  wives.
是七個
And Pleshkin? Hermaphrodite.
至於普希金? 他是雌雄同體
Once,he comes in three hours late.
有一次 他來晚了三小時
I tell him to go screw himself.
我讓他自己草自己去
He says,"Why do you think I'm three hours late?
他說"不然你以為我為什麼遲到"
" That's a joke,sweetheart. Feel free to laugh.
我開玩笑的 親愛的 想笑就笑吧
Is this thing on? Roll Tide!
這玩意還管用嗎? 紅潮!
Pleshkin!
普希金!
I need another one. Marty?
我還要來一杯 Marty?
Why not?
為什麼不呢?
I got my liver from a narcoleptic Vietnamese rickshaw driver.
我的肝臟來自一個患嗜睡症 騎黃包車的越南人
Evy,that's the best gift you have ever given me.
Evy 這是你送我最好的禮物
What do you mean?
什麼意思?
You,me,Jenny,a handful of little blue pills...
你 我還有Jenny 加一把藍色小藥丸
It's like the Spring Break of '43 all over again!
就像回到1943年的春假一樣
Marty,she's my granddaughter.
Marty 她是我的孫女
I know.
我知道
I have had some of the most decadent sexual encounters imaginable:
我的性愛史墮落不堪
mother/daughter,twins,triplets,Pleshkin.
和母女啊 雙胞胎啊 三胞胎啊 普希金啊
But never the elusive grandmother/granddaughter combo.
卻從沒試過罕見的祖孫檔
She's gay.
她是同性戀
It just keeps getting better.
那就更錦上添花了
Sweetheart,while-while I normally love your unique brand of depravity,
親愛的 儘管一般來說 我是喜歡你獨特墮落行為的
this is where I draw the line.
但這裡就是我的底線了
So when it's me and the plumber,it's fine.
所以我倆和水管工就沒問題?
You wanted that as much as I did.
你當時和我一樣"性奮"
I had my eye on his kidney.
我看上他的腎了
This is so exciting.
太刺激了
- Another man's bed,another man's woman,another man's... - Home!
- 別人的床 別人的馬子 別人的... - 家!
I know,it's so dirty.
我知道 太下流了
No,no,no,the garage door just opened!
不是 車庫門開了!
And here comes the car.
車車要來咯
Beep! Beep!
嗶 嗶
No,Larry's home! Get out!
不是 Larry回來了 快出去
What do I do? What do I do? Uh...
我該怎麼辦? 該怎麼辦?
Hide in the closet? Uh... under the bed?
躲衣櫃裡? 床底下?
Ooh,I could put on a wig and a dress and pretend I'm one of your friends.
我可以披上假髮和裙子 假裝是你的女性朋友
Out the window!
從窗戶出去
Right,good call.
對哦 好主意
Whoa,we are up there. Oh,beautiful view.
哇 好高哦 好漂亮的風景
Hey,is that the Hollywood sign...
那是好萊塢標誌嗎?
What happened to you?
你怎麼了?
Oh,these?
這些傷?
I was with Lyndsey last night,at her boyfriend's house,
昨晚我和Lyndsey在她男友家嘿咻
and he came home early,and I had to jump out the window.
他提早回家了 我得從窗戶跳出去
Alan Harper: Love Burglar.
Alan Harper之"愛的夜賊"
I like it better than Alan Harper: Roommate.
總比Alan Harper之"同居密友"好
It's just so much fun to be thought of as a piece of meat.
被當做性愛工具感覺真好
She doesn't care about what I think or what I say.
她不在乎我想什麼 說什麼
I know how she feels.
我感同身受
Let me ask you something.
我想問你點事
How would you like it if you were the poor schmuck being cheated on?
如果你是那個被戴綠帽的可憐蟲 你會是什麼感覺?
I've always been the poor schmuck.
我一直都是那個可憐蟲
And how did it feel?
那是什麼感覺呢?
Horrible.
很糟糕
Ha-ha,suck it,Larry!
哈哈活該 Larry!
I know you're having fun,Alan,but sooner or later,
我知道你樂在其中 Alan
somebody's gonna get hurt.
但遲早有人會受傷的
Oh,believe me,someone got hurt last night.
相信我 昨晚就有人受傷了
Boom,boom,boom!
嗙 嗙 嗙
Know what I'm saying?
懂我的意思?
Okay,from now on,
好吧 從現在開始
let's just assume that I know what you're saying and I don't like it.
就當我懂你的意思 可我一點也不喜歡
All right,you are hair-free.
好了 毛都剃光咯
You missed a spot.
你漏了一個地方
You are a dirty old man.
你真是個下流的老頭子
If I'm such a dirty old man,maybe it's time for my sponge bath.
如果我真是個骯髒的老頭 那是時候給我洗個海綿浴了
Paging Nurse Evelyn! Report to Marty's crotch with a loofah!
呼叫Evelyn護士! 帶上絲瓜絡到Marty的褲襠報到!
You ready to go?
準備好了嗎?
I'll be right with you,dear.
我馬上就來 親愛的
Where are you going?
你要去哪?
What about rubba-dub-dub,Marty's in the tub?
"啦啦幫 Marty在浴缸"怎麼辦?
I'll be right back. We're just going to the spa.
我很快就回來 我們只是去做Spa
Yeah,Marty,you'll be happy.
是啊 Marty 你會很喜歡的
When I she comes back,she'll have less hair than your ears.
她回來時 全身的毛會比你耳朵裡的還少
But this is date night.
但今晚是約會之夜
I'll be back by 8:00.
8點前我會回來的
That's after  Wheel. I'll be asleep.
太晚了 我都睡著了
I'll make it up to you in the morning.
那我明早補償你
I'm 91-and-a-half!
我都91歲半了!
I can't plan that far ahead!
不能做這麼長遠的計劃!
That was amazing.
太棒了
It was. You seen my underwear?
是的 你看到我內褲了嗎?
Do you mean... these?
你是指 這條嗎?
You know what? Keep 'em.
算了 你留著吧
Ooh,thank you.
謝謝
Where you going?
你去哪?
What do you mean? Home. We're done.
什麼意思? 回家啊 我們完事了
So it's just wham,bam,thank you...
你就只會說 嘿咻 謝謝你...
incredibly powerful,yet sensitive lover man?
無比強大又敏感的愛人?
Aw,don't get my panties in a bunch.
還有 別把我的內褲弄成一團
I'm serious. We never talk.
我說真的 我們都沒好好聊聊
Because we're not dating.
因為我們不是在談戀愛
I thought you were okay with this.
我以為你不介意的
I am. That doesn't mean we can't take an interest in each others' lives.
是的 可我們還是能相互瞭解下啊
For example,did you know Charlie had a daughter?
比如說 你知道Charlie有個女兒嗎
- Really? - Yeah!
- 真的嗎? - 是的!
That's great! You can talk to her.
好極了 你去和她聊吧
Fine. Whatever.
好吧 隨便
Oh,for the love of God! What do you want from me?
受不了了! 你想我怎麼樣?
Well,if you must know,she's coming over for dinner tomorrow night,
你要真想知道 她明天會來家裡吃晚餐
and I just thought that maybe you'd like to join us.
我想著你可能會想來
Dinner? Seriously?
晚餐? 有沒搞錯?
Forget I mentioned it.
當我沒說
Okay,look,I'll see what I can do.
好吧 我盡量
- Really? - I'll try.
- 真的? - 我盡量
Oh,thank you. You've made me so happy.
謝謝 我好開心
Great. See ya.
行了 拜
I should've just bought a damn vibrator.
當初不如買個該死的震動棒
Here ya go,Marty.
給你 Marty
Just the way you like it-- scotch and Metamucil.
你的最愛-- 威士忌和便秘舒
Why aren't we eating? It's almost 6:00.
怎麼還不開飯? 都快6點了
Where are we,France?
我們在哪 法國嗎?
We're waiting for Alan's girlfriend.
我們在等Alan的女朋友
I thought he was Alan's girlfriend?
我以為他是Alan的女朋友
No. I own the house. It's actually a funny story.
不 我是房主 這事說來好笑
I was on the beach and I went...
我當時在沙灘上正準備...
Don't care.
沒興趣
Marty,don't be rude.
Marty 放禮貌些
I'm sorry. Low blood sugar.
不好意思 低血糖犯了
Plus,I really don't care.
另外 我真的沒興趣
Unbelievable.
不敢相信
Lyndsey's not answering any of my calls and she hasn't returned any of my texts.
Lyndsey不接電話也不回短信
I told you you were gonna get hurt.
我說過你會受傷害的
You know what? I'm gonna go get her.
知道嗎? 我要去找她
And don't try to stop me.
都別攔著我
- Okay. - No problem.
- 好的 - 沒問題
Now that buzzkill is gone... anyone want to get high?
掃興鬼終於走了... 有人想嗨一下嗎?
Roll joint!
一品大麻!
You think Alan's gonna mind that we started without him?
你們說Alan會介意 我們沒等他就開飯嗎?
Who's Alan?
Alan是誰?
You know... I think I banged Lucille Ball in this house.
知道不... 我好像在這屋裡上過Lucille Ball
She was my second-favorite redhead.
她是我第二喜愛的紅髮女人
Thank you.
謝謝
Wait a second. It's night.
等會兒 都大晚上了
Why am I still here?
我怎麼還在這兒?
I'll see you tomorrow.
明天見
Are you okay to drive?
你這樣能開車嗎?
I'm fine.
沒問題
Well,let me know when you get home.
好吧 到家了跟我說一聲
I'm home.
到家了啊
Your father would've loved this night.
你父親一定會喜歡這個夜晚的
We're all drunk,we're all high,and Alan's not here.
我們全都喝醉了 嗨大了 而且Alan也不在
Wait-- who's Alan?
停 Alan是誰?
You know what we should do tomorrow?
知道我們明天該去幹嘛?
Go to the Malibu Police Station.
去馬裡布警察局
They took more pictures of your dad than I did.
警察給他拍的照片比我還多
Again? I want to stay home and play naked  Jeopardy.
鬧哪樣? 我想在家玩裸版智力問答
I want to spend time with my daughter.
我想多陪陪我女兒
Granddaughter.
是孫女
Oh,please,nobody's buying that.
得了吧 沒人信
I am going into the living room,Evelyn. I suggest you push me there.
我要去客廳 Evelyn 我建議你推我過去
We need to talk.
我們得談談
Be back in a minute. There's a 50-50 chance he won't remember what he wants.
一會兒就回來 有一半可能他會忘記他要幹嘛
If you're gonna talk about me,you shouldn't shave my ears first.
早知要說我壞話 你就不該刮我耳毛
He's great.
他可真棒
Wonder what it's like to be 91.
真想知道活到91歲是啥感覺
I imagine that you're wet in the places you used to be
我猜應該是 你該干的地方濕了
dry and dry in the places you used to be wet.
該濕的地方干了
What's wrong?
怎麼了?
Your granddaughter is coming between us...
你孫女夾在我們中間了...
and not in the good way.
不是那種讓人享受的夾法
Look,Marty,she just came into my life.
聽著 Marty 她剛剛進入我的生活
And believe it or not,
信不信由你
I wasn't always the best mom to Charlie or-or the other one.
我從來都不是一個稱職的母親 無論是對Charlie還是那誰
Jennifer is my second chance.
Jennifer是我的第二次機會
You got to make a choice. It's me or the kid.
你必須做出選擇 我 還是那孩子
I love you,Marty,but I have to pick my granddaughter.
我愛你 Marty 但我必須選我孫女
You know,I have $400 million.
你要知道我有4億美金身家
I'm not saying it isn't close.
你倆伯仲難分 我的選擇很艱難
It's over.
都結束了
Okay,I'm bluffing. I really miss you.
好吧 我在虛張聲勢 我真的很想你
I miss you too,money... honey.
我也想你 錢愛... 親愛的
Maybe I can make it up to you.
也許我能補償給你
If you can make it down to me,you can make it up to me.
如果你從我下面入手 就能補償給我
Something tells me that Marty doesn't want me around.
我感覺Marty不喜歡我在身邊
What?!  I can't imagine anyone not wanting you around.
啥?! 我想不出誰會不喜歡你在身邊
Really? Because I'm pretty sure I'm staying at my grandmother's
真的? 我相當肯定 我之所以住在奶奶家
because you don't want me around.
是因為你不想讓我在你這
No...  Maybe... Yes...
不...  可能吧... 是的...
I get it.
我理解
You already have Alan.
你已經有Alan了
I do.
是啊
Hey,do you think I'd look good in a jumpsuit?
你覺得我穿連衣褲會好看嗎?
You'd look good in anything.
你穿什麼都好看
That's 'cause I'm good-looking.
那是因為我人美
I pretend like I don't know.
我裝作不知道的
Seriously,if you want privacy,then why do you have a roommate?
說真的 如果你想要私人空間 為什麼還留他做室友?
Oh,you know,Alan's way more than a roommate.
你懂的 Alan遠不止是室友
He's my best friend.
他是我最好的朋友
He was there for me when I was all alone.
當我寂寞孤單時 他總陪在我身邊
He even took me into my own house.
是他收留我在我自己房子裡的
You know,him and-and his stoner son and his horny mom and your dead dad.
你懂的 他和他那嗑嗨了的兒子 還有他的色老娘和你的死老爹
I mean,they've really become my family.
他們都成我的家人了
Mine,too.
也是我的
I guess that means you're becoming part of my family.
我猜這意味著 你也成為我家人了
I'm the most masculine person in this house.
我是這家裡最有男子氣概的了
I like you,Jenny.
我很喜歡你 Jenny
I like you,Walden.
我也喜歡你 Walden
If you were a chick,I would totally do you.
你要是個女人 我絕對會上你
Aw! You,too!
彼此彼此!
Hey,you're welcome to crash here any time you need a break from Evelyn and...
嘿 歡迎你任何時候來過夜 如果你想從Evelyn和...
91-and-a-half shades of gray.
91歲半灰之間逃出來喘口氣的話
Seriously?
真的嗎?
Yeah. You know,I was thinking about putting in a home gym,but big deal.
我原先想在家裡弄個健身房 但那不重要了
I'd rather have a Jenny than a gym.
寧要Jenny不要健身
You and me both.
這點我們一樣
I get it. 'Cause Jim and gym are homonyms and
我懂了 因為Jim和健身房是"同音詞"
you're a "hamma-sexual""
而你又是 "同性戀"
It's awfully quiet in there. Did they leave?
那邊好安靜 他們走了嗎?
I don't know. Let me go look.
不知道誒 我去看看
I shouldn't have looked.
我不該去看的
No matter what she says,do not cry.
不論她說什麼 忍住眼淚不要哭
You're the prize here.
你才是戰利品
Alan,what are you doing here?
Alan 你在這兒幹嘛?
What are  you  doing here?
你在這兒幹嘛?
You're supposed to be at my house for dinner.
你應該在我家吃晚餐的
I said I would try.
我說了我會盡量
And I said I wouldn't cry.
我也說了我不會哭
And I guess we're both liars now.
我想我們現在都成騙子了
Would you keep it down? Larry's here.
你能小點聲嗎? Larry在家呢
What? You don't want him to hear your whore?
什麼? 你不想他聽到你的慰安夫?
'Cause that's all I am to you-- your whore!
因為對你來說我就是-- 你的慰安夫!
We agreed this was just about sex.
我們說好只談性不談愛的
Well,forgive me for falling in love.
好吧 原諒我墜入愛河
Alan,if you don't leave right now,you're never gonna see this again.
Alan 如果你還不走 就甭想再看到這個
Call at your convenience.
方便的時候給我打個電話
I'll get that.
我來開門
It's probably Lyndsey looking for a little morning wood to start her fire.
可能是Lyndsey大早上 想找點乾柴點燃她的烈火
Know what I'm saying?
你們懂?
I know what you're saying,I just don't know  why  you're saying it.
我知道你在說什麼 就是不知道你為啥要說
Uh,hello?
你好?
Mackenzie,you lying bitch!
Mackenzie 你個謊話精!
Congo,my ass! Don't run! You don't want to run!
剛果你大爺! 別跑! 別想跑掉!
Yeah,it feels like home again.
沒錯 又找到家的感覺了
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組-歆組=- 翻譯: 霄霄 午桑 小Jake 校對: Baby 小貂 時間軸: 雅貝
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET- 雅贝
-------------------------- 本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用 禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負 --------------------------
Two And a Half Men  Season 11 Episode 2 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
好漢兩個半 第11季 第2集 完 720p唳掛覃苺ㄩC.Ronaldo